Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for all your support.
Ending
Hello! Stay this time with Ruri Tamura from Juice- Juice and Yoh-Utano Sato from BEYOOOOONDS and Seasonings.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Now, BEYOOOOONDS is going to be the first one to appear on this Halo! Ste on April 12, when it will be distributed,
BEYOOOOONDS released a new single, "Seek yo Fate Traveler-san, Yume wo Yoru Kakeru Yozora ni" (Seek yo Fate Traveler-san, In the Night Sky Where You Cannot Even Draw a Dream).
Congratulations!
The song "Seek Me, Fate's Traveler" has a very cool sound, funky and bluesy, but the theme of the lyrics is the journey of the three nests,
The lyrics are about a traveler in three nests, and the song has a very cute gap between the two.
The lyrics of "Yume no yokozora ni (I can't even draw a dream in the night sky)" are very straight and warm, and the arrangement by the brass band is very good,
The brass band arrangement and the piano by Honaka Kobayashi, a member of the band, make it a very beautiful song.
Both songs are very BEYOOOOONDS-like,
Both songs are very typical of BEYOOOOONDS, but they are completely different from each other, and you can see a really cute and energetic BEYOOOOONDS in one song, and in the other song, a magnificent song,
I think you will enjoy the gap between the two songs,
If you read the lyrics carefully, you will find them very interesting,
I hope you will listen to it as much as possible.
This song is also performed live,
The song is performed live, but it was written by an adult who was destined to be the original songwriter,
There are hand gestures called "addition, subtraction, multiplication, and division,
I would be very happy if you could learn them and dance along with us.
Both Juice-Juice and BEYOOOOONDS have started their spring tours.
The tour is called Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour Juice-Juice,
The title is written "10th" and reads "Juice".
It is our 10th anniversary year, so the contents of the tour are very suitable for it.
I am looking forward to having fun and doing my best.
BEYOOOOONDS's concert tour is called "BEYOOOOONDS Concert Tour NEO BEYO,
We are going on a spring tour under the title of "BEYOOOOONDS Concert Tour NEO BEYO",
NEO means "new" or "fresh" in Japanese,
We are taking on a lot of challenges that we have never taken on before,
We are taking on a lot of challenges that we have never taken on before, so I hope you will enjoy the tour.
Please take a look at this video first.
Please enjoy it.
ED]
I can't even draw a dream I won't let the night sky
I'll walk while humming your favorite melody
I won't let the night sky where I can't even sing of love
It's wonderful that you were born as you
I'll walk while humming the melody you love
I won't let the night sky become a place where you can't even dream
So many stars love you
I can't draw anything, even when I can't believe it
Don't forget that you were born on such a beautiful star
Thank you, I'm sorry, take care, bye-bye
I want to hold them all in my arms
Running away won't make it happen, the moment we're here now
You and I are sharing a song, it's a miracle
La la la la...
It's hot, it's tiny, it tickles my chest
I want to hold on to that thought, to hold on to it, it's a precious piece.
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiroyuki
I won't let the night sky become a place where you can't even draw a dream
I'll walk while humming your favorite melody
I won't let the night sky where I can't even sing of love
It's wonderful that you were born as you
If it's a world where you don't feel that way, then fine
I've collected scraps of words and filled them up
I want to sing to you, Lara
No one can pollute the night sky, it's watching over you
I love you for always living your life to the fullest
I can't make my dreams come true in the moment of being here now
That you were born as you
It only happens once in a long, long time
It's a beautiful thing
[Applause]
Let's do our best tomorrow.
This is Halo! Stay!
From here we're going to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Riho says she loves collecting cosmetics.
What are some of the items you are collecting this season?
Pink eye shadow.
What is your favorite part of the makeup process?
When I put on a highlighter.
What is your most memorable bike ride, in reference to your latest single?
A nearby riverbank.
Tell us about the moment when you felt like you were born on such a beautiful planet.
When I was at an outdoor event at Lake Yamanakako Den.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of the Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year.
Which song would you like to choreograph?
Platonic Planet by Juice-Juice.
Oh! Thank you very much.
I'm curious about your last question.
Why Platonic Planet?
I love it.
Oh, yeah.
I like it so much that when I do choreography, if the song has lyrics.
I like to make choreography that matches the lyrics.
I really like the lyrics of Platonic Planet.
I like the lyrics of Platonic Planet, so I thought I'd like to study them.
I'd like to take a look at it.
I also like it a lot.
I personally like Platonic Planet very much.
I'm also interested in your choreography.
I was also surprised that your favorite part of your makeup is the highlighter.
I was quite surprised that you like to use a highlighter when you do your makeup.
I didn't know that was true.
You seem to have a lot of things?
Yes, I do.
I have one favorite.
When I can say "highlight".
It's easy to see how my face has changed.
I really enjoy looking in the mirror.
I have the image that you are really good at makeup.
When I was talking to her, I thought she looked so cute with big eyes.
I thought I would like to try highlighting too.
Questions for Ms. Dambala were asked after the VTR.
Hallo! STE.
BEYOOOOONDS new single Seek me, Mr. Fateful Traveler Now on tour
I have the night sky that can't be polluted now
FIONA'S NEW SINGLE
Yozora no Yume wo Kukerunai ha NOW ON SALE
Limited MOMENT
Burnt out with my whole life
I am the one who creates me
ALL FEVER
Which one is loved?
Common sense says this way
Which one's the backstage trick?
So tell me.
LOVE IT!
HUMAN LIFE
You can't lose, you can't lose, you can't lose
Regretful Passing by
Angerme NEW ALBUM
BIG LOVE
NOW ON SALE
HARO! STE.
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Danbara a question.
Yes, I do.
Mr. Dambala says he loves to eat.
What is the seasonal delicacy you definitely want to eat this time of year?
Bamboo shoots.
Mr. Dambala enjoys watching videos.
What kind of videos do you watch most often these days?
Videos of people cooking.
2023 is Juice-Juice's 10th anniversary year!
Do you have any personal goals for this year?
I want to sing a lot.
What kind of hair arrangement would suit you best?
High twin-tail hair.
What is your favorite song from Hello!
Project, which song would you like to sing?
Juice-Juice's "Be honest and sweet".
Thank you very much.
I have a lot of questions that I'd like to ask you.
First of all, I'm really sorry.
I know this is a personal question, but...
I'm not very good at arranging hair.
Really?Really?
I don't get that image at all.
I just wanted to ask.
I love twintails.
When a girl with long hair wears twin-tails
It's a little bit cool.
I thought that Chan, the singer, would definitely look good with twin-tail hair.
I thought I'd like to see a kind of cool twin-tail hairstyle.
I'd love to try it!
Please call me anytime.
Yes, and...
I like bamboo shoots, too.
I especially like takikomi-gohan.
I always make takikomi gohan for all seasons, and I think bamboo shoots are delicious in spring.
I wanted to make taketoko gohan in spring.
I hope to see it on your blog someday!
Hello! Stay tuned for more after this!
But I shouldn't have known how I felt
You're my friend
I wish someone would listen to my feelings like this
You know everything about me
I can't get any closer
Because you and I are friends
I've screamed so loud
Running out of breath
We've met in this town and we've spent every minute together
Spring, summer, fall, winter
The sunsets were so bright
That we wished for but could never reach
In the memories that are always precious to me
I see your smile
I love you day by day
Thank you for watching
If it were an unknown year, I could have said I love you
You're my friend
Why did we become friends, my friend?
I love you so much I can't stop crying
I don't want to lose you
If I can be with you, I'll stay like this
When I cried with a small voice
When I was all alone and lonely
You ruled me more tenderly than anyone else.
You're the most important person in my life.
If my feelings could be understood
If my feelings could reach you
The sky I'm looking up and the words I'm saying
Would shine brighter and brighter
I love you day by day
I've shouted out loud
Running out of breath
I love you day by day
We meet in the city and spend time together
Spring, summer, fall, winter
The sunsets were so bright
That we wished for but could never reach
I'll always have those precious memories
I see your smile
I love you day by day
Thank you for watching!
Sound Hodori 🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
Instagram Halo! Ste Hodori
Instagram Halo! Ste. Hodori
To all of you who support me
I am surprised to realize that the moment has come for me to depart from the position of having seen off my fellow classmates and seniors.
I am not sure if I have summed it up well, but I have written my thoughts in a letter, so let me read it.
First of all, I am very grateful to be able to perform at the event titled "Graduation Live".
I am also grateful that we will be able to borrow the stage at the HinaFest so that many people will be able to see the 12 of us, Tsubaki,
I'm also very happy to be able to close the show as the last performance of Kiki Asakura's idol show.
It is because of all of you here, as well as all of you who support us on a daily basis, that today's stage is here,
I am here today because of all of you who are here and all of you who support us on a daily basis. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Hello Project was the first time in my life that I was able to express my own desires, and it all started with Bono.
It was the first time for me to be absorbed in something, to be interested in music, and to fall in love with an idol,
I was a young girl, but I quickly became intuitively convinced that this was what I wanted to do with my life, and I desperately followed the sparkling Hello Project with all my might.
I was desperately following the sparkling Hello Project with all my might, and when I decided that I wanted to be a part of it, or rather, that I was determined to become a part of it, my parents were so surprised to see how serious I was about it,
That is why they have always supported me from the time of my audition to this point.
I think it was because they were close to me that I was able to go straight to what I wanted to do and concentrate on this activity.
I would like to applaud my family, because I would not be where I am today without them.
Thank you for being there for me, including my dogs, who I love and cherish so much.
I also want to thank my family and my dogs, whom I love and love very much, for being by my side and watching over me,
The fellow students who were aiming for their debut, and the staff and teachers who treated me with love and sometimes severity, gave me a lot of color in my life, and this is where my idol life began.
My life as an idol began here,
I was so selflessly taking on the challenges that lay ahead of me. In the spring of 2015, Tsubaki Factory was formed.
Looking back now, the six of us still looked so innocent. A group from the ground up, we get to spend more time together than school friends or family.
It was the first time I had ever met a member of the group, and I was filled with wonder.
At the same time, as someone who still had to learn the basics, I honestly felt that the time that had passed by so quickly, and I felt sorry for the people around me.
That is why I wanted to do my best to give an imposing performance that would not embarrass anyone who saw it, and since I was chosen as a member, I was determined to make it a success.
Since Tsubaki Factory's activities started, I have been able to learn singing and dancing in a place that I love.
I was very happy to be able to learn how to sing and dance in a place that I love, to challenge myself on stage at times, and to have live performances in my daily life.
Just as we were gaining momentum, we had to take a break due to hernia treatment.
Even after returning to the group, I was not able to participate in all the songs right away,
I think I often made people feel uneasy. I had my share of regrets, but it was because of these experiences that I had a chance to look at myself again, and most importantly, I realized how much support I had from everyone who supported me.
When I was not able to do what I wanted and lacked self-confidence, you all recognized me,
I was not able to do what I wanted, and I was not confident in myself, but you all acknowledged me and told me that you liked me more than I did.
I felt that if I was needed, I would do my best.
I am most proud of the fact that you have supported me. Thank you very much.
I am so proud of you all for being so kind and warm to me, even though I should be in the opposite position.
I know it has been a tumultuous period for you, but thank you for supporting me this far.
And to my dear members who have always been by my side, just like all of you.
I am surrounded by you all at every moment of my life, and because of you all, Spaki Factory is possible, and I am proud to be a part of it.
Spaki Factory is possible because of all of you, and I have been able to work this far.
Riko, Risa, Kiso, Ami, and Yume, who have been with me since the beginning.
They are the people who make me feel at ease and comfortable.
They make me feel at ease.
There were a lot of things we had to overcome
Thank you from the beginning.
I don't know if you guys are aware of it, but...
I'm glad you've come to spoil me like I'm the youngest
I'm glad that you've started to let me be pampered.
And Mizuho, Saori, and Mao have joined us as additional members, though,
I think I was so excited about Tsubaki Factory from the very beginning that I forgot about them.
Without these three, I honestly don't think we would have lasted this long.
They have made the group that much more exciting,
Thank you for loving us all above all.
Thank you for your kindness.
Yumi, Shiori, Marin, and Reno were our first juniors.
I think their joining has also had a great impact on Tsubaki Factory and led to our individual growth.
We have had many happy events, such as our dream of performing at the Nippon Budokan, a solo concert at a concert hall, a No. 1 ranking in the Oricon Ranking, and a performance with a live band.
Thank you very much for joining us and making a new entrance for us,
Above all, everyone is honest and nice. I am attracted by their straightforwardness,
I am already looking forward to the future of the four of them, who have so many weapons of their own.
I hope they will continue to lead Tsubaki, regardless of whether they are juniors or not. I wish you all the best.
As we continue to grow year by year.
I feel that the circle of Tsubaki Factory is expanding, and I wonder how we should show it,
I feel that the circle of Tsubaki Factory is widening every year. Thanks to the support of many people throughout the years, Tsubaki Factory is where it is today,
Tsubaki Factory is here today thanks to the support of many people. They have given us hints to move forward, sometimes harshly, and they have thought a lot about things that we could not even see,
Thank you very much.
We are leaving such a place filled with love, and we will be moving on to a different path.
I think the biggest change in me is that I have shifted from a sense of responsibility to a sense of enjoyment.
Thank you very much for the nine years that you have made me realize so many important things.
Tsubaki Factory will continue to be
Tsubaki Factory will continue to be the best group and will never fail to entertain me. I have the experience and memories of walking with the best friends on my side.
I am sure that I will be fine in my new environment, even if I go solo. So let me say this.
I'm not saying goodbye, I'm going. Let's continue to make camellia flowers bloom in each other's respective places.
April 2, 2023, Tsubaki Factory
Juki Tsubaki
Hallo! Ste.
Ruri Tamura of Juice-Juice, BEYOOOOONDS, and Tana Sato of Seasonings present "Halo! STE!
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit is currently underway.
Juice-Juice is currently holding its 10th Anniversary Tour, so we haven't been able to sing all of Juice-Juice's songs from the past 10 years,
But the tour is filled with the songs from the past 10 years.
I think you will be able to see a lot of songs from the early days of Juice-Juice as well as the current Juice-Juice songs.
What about BEYOOOOONDS?
BEYOOOOONDS is titled Neovio, the subtitle of the tour,
I think this concert will be filled with many things that you have never seen in BEYOOOOONDS before,
I hope you will come and enjoy the concert with excitement.
BEYOOOOONDS will be performing at the Nippon Budokan for the second time on May 15.
I am looking forward to it.I am looking forward to it.
This will be our second time, so we hope to enjoy ourselves even more than last time,
I hope we can make it even more enjoyable than the last time, and I hope the audience will like Beyoncé even more.
We are really looking forward to BEYOOOOONDS's Budokan concert.
We are really looking forward to it, and we, Juice-Juice, are also going to perform at the Budokan.
It will be held on May 29.
It will be our 10th Anniversary, and we would like to make it a very exciting event,
Please come and see BEYOOOOONDS's Juice-Juice.
We look forward to seeing you there.
In addition, BEYOOOOONDS will be performing with Pacific Philharmonia Pop Stokyo on May 2.
Pacific Philharmonia Pop Stokyo and BEYOOOOONDS will be giving a concert called Biophonic on May 2.
Biophonic concert with Pacific Philharmonia Pop Stokyo.
This will be our second concert,
The last time was in Hyogo Prefecture, and this time we will be performing at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space.
Pacific Philharmonia Pop Stokyo has been a great help to us in the night sky when we couldn't even draw a dream,
I am sure we will be able to show you a new side of ourselves,
Please check it out.
Now, we are going to sing our last song.
Let's get excited to the very end, everyone!
Yay!
Here is the last song that the 12 of us will sing with Kitsu.
Happy Cracker!
Cracker! Cracker! Happy days!
Bright dancing sky, I wanna be shy
Hammer, come on, next time
Colorful Jump You A!
I know how you feel, but
I know how you feel, but you're still so gloomy, it's not the end of your youth
Time's up, time's up, time's up, time's up, time's up, time's up
I'll cheer you on
I'll cheer you on as you take in the familiar scenery that's turning peachy
I'll give birth to you, though anxiety shakes my heart
At least for this moment
Yeah, let your heart soar
Clap Clap Clap Clap Happy Day
I wish I could celebrate the sky that dances brightly
To the days when we'll travel with love
Clap Clap Clap Clap Happy Day
I want to celebrate with a big show on a sunny corner
With a smile on my face
To a colorful exchange
Clap Clap Clap Clap Happy Day
Step by Step Remembering the days before yesterday
We never met yesterday and we still missed it
In the same room, at the same desk
The bond I built with my friends Forever
Those days that become courage Forever
If I stop even if I'm alone from tomorrow
The past that we've been together, we've known each other
Moment by moment, we'll just take it a little bit further
Today is the end of the time when I was able to be selfish
To the new you
Ga Ga Ga Ga Happy Day
I want to celebrate the sky that's dancing so brightly
Aatch, aatch, aistei
To the one who's leaving
Ga Ga Ga Ga Happy Day
I want to celebrate with a big show on a sunny corner
With a blooming smile
Yes, spring, summer, fall, winter, year round vacation Parapper
Every day shows you where you belong
Every day shows you a brighter place than the one you're in now
Enjoy the life you're living
Life's gonna be so bright and colorful
Ga Ga Ga Ga Happy Day
The sky is dancing so brightly, I wish I could be in the sun
Ach, ach, ach, love...
Spring, summer, fall, winter, all the year round vacation parapper
Happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy
We are the brand new ace, the best brand new ace
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
That was Swatchatree.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you very much for your support so far.
Project, and I have been able to experience many things with everyone,
I am very happy to have been able to experience so many precious things with everyone,
I love singing and expressing myself through performance,
I love singing and expressing myself in performance, so I will do my best to show you various aspects of myself even as a solo performer.
I look forward to your continued support.
Ruru Danbara of Chus Chus and Yutana Sato of BEYOOOOONDS Seasonings will be presenting Halo! Stay!
It is time for us to say goodbye. Here is an announcement.
Beyonc's new single "Seek yo, Fate's Traveler, Yume wa nakurenai yozora ni" (Seek yo, Fate's Traveler, You Can't Even Draw a Dream in the Night Sky) was released today.
Please check out these two songs filled with our gap.
Also released today, BEYOOOOONDS's Second Concert Tour
Please also check out the Blu-ray of "Heaven and Horns, Beauty in Autumn" which was also released today.
It is a hot concert filled with songs from the second album.
And Hello Project 2023 Spring City Circuit is underway.
Next time, Juice Chus will perform in Aichi on April 15 and in Kanagawa on April 16.
Yes, BEYOOOOONDS will perform in Kanagawa on April 22 and 23.
And on May 15, they will perform at Nippon Budokan.
The Juice Chus will also perform at the Nippon Budokan on May 29,
Please come and visit both teams.
Please come and visit the two teams.
And on May 2, we will be holding the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space's 3-year biophonic concert.
Please look forward to a live performance that is different from the usual concert with an orchestra.
Hello! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
We are still in the midst of a difficult time, but let's get through it together.
This time with Ruri Tamura of Juice Chus,
and Yoshitana Sota of BEYOOOOONDS's Seasonings.
Farewell!